{
  "name": "Vārdi matemātikā",
  "level": 1,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 501,
      "type": "select-from-text",
      "prompt": "Nospied uz 'saskaitāmais'",
      "sentence": ["3", "+", "9", "=", "12"],
      "selectableParts": [0, 2, 4],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 502,
      "type": "select-from-text",
      "prompt": "Nospied uz 'saskaitītājs'",
      "sentence": ["4", "+", "8", "=", "12"],
      "selectableParts": [0, 2, 4],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 503,
      "type": "select-from-text",
      "prompt": "Nospied uz 'summa'",
      "sentence": ["6", "+", "6", "=", "12"],
      "selectableParts": [0, 2, 4],
      "correctAnswer": 4
    },
    {
    "id": 504,
    "type": "select-from-text",
    "prompt": "Nospied uz 'saskaitāmais'",
    "sentence": ["7", "+", "2", "=", "9"],
    "selectableParts": [0, 2, 4],
    "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
    "id": 505,
    "type": "select-from-text",
    "prompt": "Nospied uz 'saskaitītājs'",
    "sentence": ["5", "+", "6", "=", "11"],
    "selectableParts": [0, 2, 4],
    "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
    "id": 506,
    "type": "select-from-text",
    "prompt": "Nospied uz 'summa'",
    "sentence": ["8", "+", "7", "=", "15"],
    "selectableParts": [0, 2, 4],
    "correctAnswer": 4
    },
    {
    "id": 507,
    "type": "select-from-text",
    "prompt": "Nospied uz 'saskaitāmais'",
    "sentence": ["10", "+", "3", "=", "13"],
    "selectableParts": [0, 2, 4],
    "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
    "id": 508,
    "type": "select-from-text",
    "prompt": "Nospied uz 'saskaitītājs'",
    "sentence": ["2", "+", "5", "=", "7"],
    "selectableParts": [0, 2, 4],
    "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
    "id": 509,
    "type": "select-from-text",
    "prompt": "Nospied uz 'summa'",
    "sentence": ["9", "+", "4", "=", "13"],
    "selectableParts": [0, 2, 4],
    "correctAnswer": 4
    },
    {
    "id": 510,
    "type": "select-from-text",
    "prompt": "Nospied uz 'saskaitītājs'",
    "sentence": ["1", "+", "8", "=", "9"],
    "selectableParts": [0, 2, 4],
    "correctAnswer": 2
    }
  ]
}
